wondex.com 2018-12-14

# Privacy Policy

### Website Visitors

Wondex.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Wondex.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Wondex.com’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Wondex.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

Wondex.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Wondex.com does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. 

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Wondex.com’s websites choose to interact with Wondex.com in ways that require Wondex.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Wondex.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with Wondex.com by purchasing a service are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Wondex.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfil the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Wondex.com. Wondex.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

### Aggregated Statistics

Wondex.com may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its websites. Wondex.com may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Wondex.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Wondex.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Wondex.com’s behalf or to provide services available at Wondex.com’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organisations may be located outside of your home country; by using Wondex.com’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Wondex.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Wondex.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Wondex.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Wondex.com, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of the Wondex.com website and have supplied your email address, Wondex.com may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Wondex.com and our products. Wondex.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorised access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Wondex.com uses cookies to help Wondex.com identify and track visitors, their usage of Wondex.com website, and their website access preferences. Wondex.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Wondex.com’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Wondex.com’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

### Privacy Policy Changes

Wondex.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Wondex.com’s sole discretion. Wondex.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
